[Music]
hi Welcome to our business Central
launch event uh release 2024 wave 1
today our session is about e invoice
matching with co-pilot uh my name is B
abusada I'm a software engineer at
business Central and I'm joined today
with Alexander thank you while my name
is Alexander toic and I product manager
responsible for this feature actually
both of us we are responsible for this
feature together with our bigger team
let's show you what we talk today uh
first we'll make short introduction not
only uh about matching uh e document e
voice matching uh copilot but about
co-pilot how we working with that then
we will show process flow and then the
most important part end to end demo
while will show
you okay um first we want to emphasize
that e invoice matching with co-pilot is
in public preview that me this is still
not General available it will be in all
your environments in Cloud but as a
public
preview um if you look more at
deployment this is available only in the
B Center online so no on Prem Solutions
it is available in 2024 release way one
uh roll out will start uh with update
24.0 it will be available in all regions
globally except Canada because of some
regulatory um issues and roll out we
start with us environments about
languages currently this is available in
all type of uh English languages it can
be tried you can try using in other
languages but officially this is uh
something what we support we support
officially English language and all our
tests are pass without any problem with
English language about pricing what we
can say currently this is available
uh with standard B Central license both
essential premium without any additional
cost
um what is important to know uh when we
talk about that um Microsoft and B
center team we designed all this feature
uh ground up of Microsoft value
responsible AI standard Microsoft uh
around on a trust and um this is not
there is no difference with this
co-pilot features inside the B Central
and this one feature in bus Central our
fundamental promises are that your data
are is your data uh as a customer you
will control your data we will not take
your data we will not train our models
uh our foundational AI model aser AI
with your data your data are your data
um you're absolutely protected with
every step the most comprehensive
Enterprise compliance Security Control
in industry and every step of the way we
apply Microsoft responsible AI standards
to ensure this feature is safe for all
our customers when say our customer our
Microsoft customers and your customers
as partners and their
data so let's move to the
functionality why we started with
co-pilot on previous uh wave we deliver
uh eent framework and we deliver on top
of that integration with external
Services it was really nice feature we
deliver when we really proud what we
deliver in such a short uh term but we
need to admit we had some small missing
features there we still have space to
improve and we are doing this and this
way is a proof that we are we are
continuing to investing in um this
functionality and we will continue in
the future as well but what is what is
what was the biggest issue just imagine
you're working a purchase process and
you don't want to create purchase
invoice you're working with purchase
orders you have uh many items and you
are working with inventory and you want
to post separately received and invoice
so you must work with purchase orders
now you received electronic invoice from
your vendor and you cannot match with
this purchase order you could as I
mentioned previously you could create
purchase invoice but if you work with
purchase order it was a blocker you
couldn't do this um
so uh there's more issues this is not
only to
connect sometimes it can be line one to
one sometimes one to many many to one
many different combination this is just
standard this is business process we
cannot say all the time yes there's
Sunshine scenario you can do one to one
similar names no this is a real real
life a real business and what we can say
as I said there is not on the time one
to one not only lines not all all the
time one to one one in voice one order
in general you can have purchased order
with maybe 10 15 uh invoices and who
knows how many differences in lines
codes are of course different
descriptions definitely different this
is probably maybe in some situation we
have sortly the same very similar
description but in most situation we
have different description in your
system internally be Central and your
vendor document of course we can use
item
references but this is not solution for
all vendors what can happen um you can
have 500 vendors and you can have
thousand of items maybe 5,000 of items
and what how you will finish with having
two millions of it references to map all
of them yes in some situation this is
possible but probably it will be really
complicated and even if you make it it
will be complicated for uh maintains in
the future so there are further
information uh what what else is this
item already received or not so we need
to have some additional cont control
what about price so there are many many
additional uh let's say blockers so it
was not so easy to make it um as I said
blocker but all the time when we have
Blocker we have solution for blocker
this is just the best uh inspiration how
to make great solution and we delivered
this solution in two parts first part
was okay let's make let's introduce new
page mapping page where you can find
from left side never mind we decide to
be on left side lines from electronic
document and right side uh lines from
purchase order good enough so you can
manually map one line with another line
one to one one to many whatever and
that's okay if you have five six lines
but if you are working with dozens of
lines or maybe with hundreds of line
wow mapping all these things especially
with different descriptions different
prices uh maybe not different but you
need to check every time your price is
okay or not if if your vendor provideed
different PR from what he already
promised so it can be really complicated
and now what we have we have unblocked
situation so you can work but not the
perfect case not the perfect scenario
but there is a magic we decided let's
introduce
copilot now copilot can do many things
and now if you do if you run copilot you
will see this in our demo it will be
really just a magic syst automatically
connect what you have electronic
document what you have in your purchase
order system will connect lines and
that's it you can be really happy and
you can work and now I cannot say there
is no accurate measuring I made some my
tests with the some 20 lines in a
purchase order and purchase voice it was
one to one so not so complicated pretty
straightforward when I did it manually
but doing manually comparing with
co-pilot it was more than 50 times
slower slower than you are doing
manually of
course Goa Pilot We increase your
efficiency many many times and now this
is one document now multiply this with
10 documents per day multiply this with
30 days okay 22 days per month and you
can see how much time and maybe
Workforce you can save this is
definitely great functionality great
example how to use um uh G GPT model now
just to finish uh this part um as I said
this is not all the time one to one we
are enable just to repeat myself one to
one one to many many to one and how it
works you will see in demo but first
what we are trying to do we try to save
your time and every time if system can
find similarity 80 or more per
similarity description system will not
ask GPT at all it will be automatically
connected so that's so far so good but
if you cannot if there is different
descriptions complicated for understand
what is in in one document what is
another Co co-pilot will uh run our llm
and together with some pre-processing
postprocessing uh uh features while
explain a little bit more details I will
not go so deep and system will do this
there are some additional controls as I
already mentioned a big issues big
potential issues uh you cannot invoice
more receip so we have control not to
allow you to make some mistake then uh
price by default must be 100% the same
there is no differences but if if you
want as a user you can make a setup you
will see how to do this and you can
enable for example for one one something
uh to to to make uh additional Precision
what you want to track so this is allow
as well and what we have more in a a few
roll centers we extended R centers with
additional cues to control the status if
this purchase already connected or you
need to do something manually to make it
easier and before while take his stage
with a great demo I want to show you
shortly process how it works first this
is all part you're getting electronic
invoice it will be it will create
automatically a document and now there
is one new things if your vendor is
configured to receive electronic uh to
receive purchase invoices to create
actually purchas Dev voices for example
power plant you just have some um easy
expense no no connected with items you
will configure making voice what system
will do system will look in general
leder mapping or item reference and
create purchase inv but if there is
different setup if setup is Mak an order
for this use orders making not not maybe
the right uh word then what system will
do system will first check okay if for
this vendor do we have some orders
active orders in the system if we do not
have yeah system will do yes the system
know we want to work with order system
will create new order the same as the
same model as creating purchase inv
voice but it will be ordered so you can
still separately post received any voice
but if there is some order system will
map this order using co-pilot uh match
everything and update existing purchase
order how it look like on this slide you
will see yeah we have E doent manual
matching a new page but we have co-pilot
here here already finished matching as I
said one to one one to many many to one
and now I think you want to see how this
look like in a practice so while please
show us gr demo full end scenario
absolutely all right let's actually show
you a great demo for this one but before
actually showing you a demo uh let's
start with the demo data we're going to
use to present this demo so in order in
order to set up e doent in in an easy
way for you to present or to use as a
customer or you as a partner to present
it to your customers we actually created
a demo data module in Koso demo tool and
if you're using the Kronos company that
comes out of the box you will find that
you have it already and you can go ahead
and use it uh if you have some of your
demo companies out there already you can
just go to contoso demo tool and run it
again take a couple of seconds and then
you have good enough demo data to
present co-pilot and different features
around e doent all right so now uh the
demo data assume that you during the
night have receiv received some uh E
doent from the government and these e
doents were actually mapped to a
purchase order and if you click here on
this queue in the r Center it will take
you to these six purchase order that
have matching incoming document that you
need to start mapping the lines for each
of the documents so now I want to show
you the sunshine scenario of using
co-pilot now and how easy it can get to
map lines between the two documents and
so let's do it I already have enabled
co-pilot for for for this environment
and this is a live demo so it took a
couple of seconds and it found five
lines that were actually uh mapped uh
for between the E doent and the purchase
order and let me walk you through this
nice page that you see so the first
thing you'll see the auto match lines
and in auto match lines in this scenario
it's Z out of five uh because this where
we try to basically match lines based on
the text in the description and if that
similarity is around 80% or more then we
will automatically match it otherwise we
will send it to co-pilot then co-pilot
will take all the lines that are left
over and we'll try to do semantic uh
matching between them or even literal
matching and based on that it will give
you some feedback hey this is my
proposal for you these are the lines
that we think they should match uh we
also take into account the cost of each
items um we also take into account the
available quantity uh that need to be
invoiced and basically you get a set of
proposal you also see on this side uh
the total amount with vat and without
vat and then you'll see all the lines
that basically are the proposal from
co-pilot uh I want to show you as I said
the our Sunshine scenario so I'm going
to go ahead and accept it and as you can
see this is done let's actually go ahead
and even apply this to our purchase
order let's see how fast this will take
done and keep an eye here on something
super cool is that we already picked the
vendor in Voice number and we also
updated the document date and then you
can go ahead and post it and you're done
your job is done you don't need to do
much effort after this one so let's Also
let's show it in more documents so let's
open this purchase order so the second
purchase order we got and you can see in
this one we don't have a vendor invoice
number you know we have set of lines
that are here different different items
uh different values um you will see some
of the purchase order in our demo data
some of them have discount different
price different description and in here
I also want to invoke co-pilot once more
this one it seems like it have more
lines right so yeah let's see how good
co-pilot will do matching these lines
all right it took some time and then
it's back ready and wow quite a lot more
lines and in here you will actually see
a little bit of difference because we
have already managed to match three out
of 14 of the lines uh automatically
based on text description similarity and
the rest were successfully matched by
co-pilot great uh you could also drill
down on one of the proposal to see more
details so you can see the e description
the purchase order description the cost
Etc but let's say you didn't like this
proposal you can easily just say discard
it and then you can go back to the
manual matching once more right but yeah
uh it's it's much easier when when when
you do it you know with co-pilot so one
of the thing also we we take into
account when we do the matching is the
cost so item have to exactly match but
what if you want to have like a wiggle
room where you can say if the item is
like I don't know 5% different than the
cost that I have in my purchase order
I'll accept it maybe you got a good deal
over the phone or something right so you
can easily go to purchase and payable
setup and adjust this setup value that
will allow co-pilot to change the margin
that allowed cost difference so if we
set it to like I don't know 10% then
co-pilot will accept anything within the
10% range from the original
cost uh and yeah that's it and uh if we
have different prices how we can differ
how we can uh make difference on an a
prompt if this is 100% the same or oh
yeah that's a really good question so if
if we open again the E
doent uh and uh when when you have
different prices you will see that um
that like we have different color that
will that will show you based on that
like is this was like this 100% match or
not and uh so yeah if it's like green
then we have like 100% match if it's
yellow then maybe it's still within the
same price range but it's within the
acceptable range that you have set up in
in payable and purchase setup if it's
red it mean it's outside of the range
and probably you need to manual
intervention and review the value thank
you yeah thank you I think this is uh a
great example of um how we can use
co-pilot in a real uh business in real
case so now yeah we can be really we can
be proud what we deliver of course all
the time there are space for for
improvement and we will look what we can
do more to make more co-pilots to extend
co-pilot features but this is something
what can be really good in a practice
usage especially more and more countries
requir to have electronic invoicing so
if could be really easy saving a time
saving a money of course absolutely and
now yeah probably you would like to see
if you want to test it if you want if
you can to test it uh if you want and uh
yes you can what you need to do you need
to log into to our CDX uh en environment
actually portal what you need to do just
go akms CDX and if your partner you have
access there or you will uh require
access you will get it when you create
your demo account there you just need to
open in another profile and you will use
this demo account and just login make a
trial bus Central and that's it you can
start you can start to test not only
this feature many other features there
are many other co-pilots as well uh but
what if if um if you cannot find copilot
if you try and there is no copilot first
check if copilot ni cap capability page
if this is a environment switch on so
you can use C pilot then uh another
things is this feature is active because
you will see there in a there are more
co-pilots check if e document e invoice
is matching is active or not if this is
not just activate is still not check uh
English language if English language is
my settings and if you on version 24
maybe you activated all versions so this
is enabl only from version
24 so that's it from our side but there
is always but we want to encourage you
to watch another session because as I
mentioned both of us mentioned there are
more co-pilots uh in this release and
you will see we have co-pilot for Sal
line suggestion co-pilot we have ai
powered analyze with co-pilot uh chat
with co-pilot really good amazing things
you will see when you start to use this
is a really amazing what you can get
this is definitely another level another
dimension of using of business
applications then you can extend
co-pilot using Al code so that means you
can do more by yourself in specific
specific partner situation industry
specifics maybe in some local uh things
so you can do it now by yourself and uh
we have what new design generative AI
experience and 61 is not about AI this
is about other things in documents so we
show you now how you can use co-pilot in
document matching but there is all also
manual matching in some situation maybe
you cannot use co-pilot but there is
still some good new thing new things
there not only matching but some other
news please watch this session and you
can see what is interesting connectivity
documents okay on this slide you can
find a lot of co-pilot
resources uh in general co-pilot
resources uh uh you can find uh uh with
one item with uh matching e document
matching release note information uh
learn uh about matching uh extend how to
extend co-pilot and so more and so more
and plus we have standard busy Central
resources use uh Yammer akbc Yammer go
there talk with us you have great
opportunity to discuss with us with the
people who are made in this and um yeah
we can we can talk you can send a
feedback we can do whatever we can do we
can discuss whatever you want there is
Twitter uh LinkedIn um uh office hours
monthly office hours be there and of
course BC ideas please log your ideas we
are really listening for this and we
want to get as more feedback as possible
because this is the way how we can
together improve our product how make it
the best and this is the best how we can
make uh to be the best in a I don't know
how many years do it together with us
and if you forget all of them please do
not forget this one AK msbc all so you
can find all these and much more links
dozens and dozens different links
there um before we official say thank
you uh we want to call you and to
encourage you join us q& a session both
while and I will be there it will be
approximately 7even days after busy
Center lunch event so you will have
enough time to watch all videos so you
will have a bunch of questions it will
be a great opportunity to discuss face
to face okay through teams but face to
face so you can ask you can type if you
don't want to ask orally but you can
talk with us we'll be more than open as
I said we want to get your feedback and
we want to update information because
maybe we didn't explain something
properly we will give you more
information there and
that's it for today we can say thank you
thank you yeah and hope you will
enjoy